var questions = [
  {
    'question': 'What animal transformation would allow you to \'meow\'?',
    'answers': ['cat', 'kitten', 'feline', 'kitty']
  },
  {
    'question': 'If you needed to unlock a door, what could you shapeshift into?',
    'answers': ['key', 'pick']
  },
  {
    'question': 'Say you need to hide on a man\'s face, what could you change into?',
    'answers': ['beard', 'glasses', 'moustache', 'monocle', 'hair']
  },
  {
    'question': 'If you needed to imitate someone patrolling a secure area, changing to what type of person would be appropriate?',
    'answers': ['guard', 'police', 'security', 'patrol', 'cop', 'fuzz']
  },
  {
    'question': 'In a stealth situation, you need to hear a conversation going on in a different room. What small animal transformation would be best?',
    'answers': ['fly', 'mouse', 'bug', 'insect', 'spider']
  },
  {
    'question': 'To hide in a large lawn, what could you shapeshift into?',
    'answers': ['grass', 'flower', 'plant', 'insect', 'bug', 'spider', 'leaf', 'leaves']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You are stowing away in the boot/trunk of a car. What could you become in order to remain inconspicuous?',
    'answers': ['petrol', 'gas', 'cannister', 'tire', 'wheel', 'sign', 'cone', 'bag', 'case', 'rug', 'mat']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to hide within a corporate kitchen. What type of person could you shapeshift into to prevent yourself being recognised?',
    'answers': ['chef', 'cook', 'washer', 'waiter', 'waitress', 'cleaner']
  },
  {
    'question': 'Lost in a pitch black cave, you need to be able to see in the dark. What animal transformation would work best?',
    'answers': ['owl', 'lemur', 'cat', 'kitty', 'feline', 'nocturnal', 'bat', 'dog', 'wolf', 'wolves']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to sneak through a tiny gap in a wall. What should you shapeshift into?',
    'answers': ['mouse', 'rat', 'bug', 'insect', 'ant', 'spider']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You have become stranded in a large desert and need to conserve water. What should you shapeshift into?',
    'answers': ['camel', 'cactus']
  },
  {
    'question': 'In a very cold environment, what animal shapeshift would be appropriate?',
    'answers': ['penguin', 'polar', 'seal', 'arctic']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to be hard to find and decide to hide in a haystack. What object should you change into?',
    'answers': ['needle', 'pin']
  },
  {
    'question': 'If you need to fly somewhere in the dark, what type of bird would be best?',
    'answers': ['bat', 'owl', 'prey', 'hawk']
  },
  {
    'question': 'To cross terrain very quickly, what land animal should you shapeshift into?',
    'answers': ['cheetah', 'pronghorn', 'springbok', 'wildebeest', 'lion', 'blackbuck', 'hare', 'greyhound', 'jackrabbit', 'horse']
  },
  {
    'question': 'A storage closet is the only place available to hide. What form could you adopt to hide there well?',
    'answers': ['cleaning', 'broom', 'brush', 'dust', 'brush']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to blend in as a human within a place of education. What job would be appropriate?',
    'answers': ['cleaner', 'handyman', 'technician', 'teacher', 'professor']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to travel through the sewers of a city. What could you transform into to make the job easier?',
    'answers': ['rat', 'crocodile', 'alligator', 'rodent', 'mouse']
  },
  {
    'question': 'You need to break down a door, but your current form is not strong enough. What could you transform into to assist you in this task?',
    'answers': ['hammer', 'axe', 'elephant', 'gorrila', 'fist', 'ram', 'chainsaw']
  }
];
